{
  "sorular": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Kırmızı", "Mavi", "Sarı", "Yeşil"],
      "correctAnswer": "Mavi",
      "renk": "#0000FF"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Mor", "Sarı", "Pembe", "Kırmızı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Mor",
      "renk": "#800080"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Beyaz", "Siyah", "Gri", "Kahverengi"],
      "correctAnswer": "Gri",
      "renk": "#808080"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Turuncu", "Sarı", "Kırmızı", "Pembe"],
      "correctAnswer": "Turuncu",
      "renk": "#FFA500"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Yeşil", "Mavi", "Siyah", "Mor"],
      "correctAnswer": "Yeşil",
      "renk": "#008000"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Siyah", "Mavi", "Kahverengi", "Beyaz"],
      "correctAnswer": "Siyah",
      "renk": "#000000"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Kırmızı", "Siyah", "Mavi", "Gri"],
      "correctAnswer": "Kırmızı",
      "renk": "#FF0000"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Beyaz", "Mavi", "Siyah", "Mor"],
      "correctAnswer": "Beyaz",
      "renk": "#FFFFFF"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Sarı", "Mor", "Yeşil", "Kırmızı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Sarı",
      "renk": "#FFFF00"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Kahverengi", "Sarı", "Kırmızı", "Turuncu"],
      "correctAnswer": "Kahverengi",
      "renk": "#A52A2A"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Mor", "Pembe", "Beyaz", "Kırmızı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Pembe",
      "renk": "#FFC0CB"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Mavi", "Mor", "Turuncu", "Yeşil"],
      "correctAnswer": "Mavi",
      "renk": "#0000FF"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Kırmızı", "Siyah", "Mor", "Yeşil"],
      "correctAnswer": "Kırmızı",
      "renk": "#FF0000"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Siyah", "Kırmızı", "Mavi", "Mor"],
      "correctAnswer": "Siyah",
      "renk": "#000000"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Sarı", "Yeşil", "Turuncu", "Kırmızı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Sarı",
      "renk": "#FFFF00"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Mor", "Beyaz", "Siyah", "Kırmızı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Mor",
      "renk": "#800080"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Yeşil", "Siyah", "Mavi", "Kahverengi"],
      "correctAnswer": "Yeşil",
      "renk": "#008000"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Kırmızı", "Beyaz", "Mavi", "Sarı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Beyaz",
      "renk": "#FFFFFF"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Kırmızı", "Mor", "Mavi", "Sarı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Mor",
      "renk": "#800080"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Yukarıdaki renk aşağıdakilerden hangisidir?",
      "options": ["Kahverengi", "Mor", "Mavi", "Sarı"],
      "correctAnswer": "Kahverengi",
      "renk": "#A52A2A"
    }
  ]
}
